What do you think is the biggest land
animal in Antarctica? Is it polar bears?
Seals? Penguins? This large bird I made
friends with? Nope. All of these are
technically marine animals. And polar
bears don't exist here at all. They're
only found up north in the Arctic. I'll
give you some hints. The largest land
animal in Antarctica is smaller than a
grain of rice. And weirdly, it dies
below -15 C, which is a big problem
because Antarctica gets down to -40 and
below. So, one spot it hides is inside
moss like this. Because when the snow
falls on top of the moss, it traps air.
And trapped air is an amazing insulator,
which keeps this little spot at a balmy
minus2 nearly all year long. But to
survive the deepest part of Antarctic
winter, it still has to dry itself
[music] out, squeezing nearly 70% of its
body water out like a sponge. Drum roll,
please. It's this, a mij. That is the
largest land animal on this entire
continent. But there's something else
hidden underneath this ice.